[{"answer": "I promised myself I wouldn't be so bossy. Take your time!! Was that bossy too", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do I get to vote? I'm going to tell you something I never told you before. Your feeling towards your work is one of the things I love most about you", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "How long since you've seen your daughter", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Oh, please. It's one thing being a so", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "But there was that one long close u", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "It reminded me of my last boyfriend.  Got to go", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "How come you haven't said anything? This is great, right", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What no", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Hell", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I just have to say goodbye. You have no idea how difficult that is", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I just have to say goodbye. You have no idea how difficult that is", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "It's not three weeks", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I've been an actor most of my life and this is the first time I've ever heard what the people calling the shots sound like when they're casting. So I really want to find out what, if anything, you know because what if nothing you know", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Oh, you couldn't be more wrong. And I'm not talking to you. And I don't like you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Oh...", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " 'Mr. Deeds Goes to Town?' Oh, it's a remake..", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Let's not make this about your shortcomings. I'm sure you've had enough of those conversations to last you a lifetime. What I'm..", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No, you haven't what", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No, I haven't", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Had a conversation about shortcomings..", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Very funny", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Set", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " Who are we calling", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " \"Very nice..", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What are you talking about", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Don't talk to me like this", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I can't believe I..", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "...got in this much trouble. ", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm on a roof..", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You're a...", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't think I can get into this..", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Worse. You caught me at a bad time you caused", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Go ahead. Use it in a sentence", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Look at me. I love a little redneck", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Honey..", "docId": "I_ll-Do-Anything.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "No. They're still having the party", "qsentId": 36}]